Portfolio: https://sk-portfolio.onrender.com **GitHub:** https://github.com/SRIKRISNA **LinkedIn:** www.linkedin.com/in/srikrisna/

SRIKRISHNA

Full Stack Developer (MERN)
Fresher - 8 months Trained



Email: skricode@gmail.com

Full Stack Developer Boot-camp

The 10X Academy

TRAINING

- DSA, ReactJs, NodeJs, ExpressJs, MongoDB, etc using these tech
 I developed many mini apps
- I programmed 300+ on Arrays, Control Flows, Searching, Sorting, Recursion, HashMaps, LinkedLists, Strings, Classes and Functions

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Applications (MCA) – (2015 - 2018)

Central University of Karnataka

• I secured 78.8 %

Bachelor of Computer Applications (BCA) – (2012 - 2015)

S S Tegnoor Degree College

• I secured 76.94 %

CERTIFICATIONS

Full Stack Development

The 10X Academy

 I trained MERN technologies with DSA programs

JavaScript Developer

Simplilearn

Vanilla JavaScript, DOM manipulations, etc

SKILLS

- ✓ Data Structure & Algorithms
- ✓ JavaScript (aware of TypeScript)
- ✓ ReactJs & Redux Toolkit
- ✓ NodeJs & Express
- ✓ MongoDB , MySQL, AWS S3 Bucket
- √ WordPress (3+ years)
- ✓ Shopify
- ✓ Canva Design
- ✓ HTML5 & CSS3, SCSS
- ✓ React-Bootstrap & MUI
- ✓ Git & Github
- ✓ cPanel (Server Maintenance)

PROFILE

I'm a professional who is good at programming, with an emphasis on writing clean and maintainable code. Experienced with data structure & algorithms, front-end technologies of React Js, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, backend technologies are Node Js, Express Js, Mongo DB and designing optimal solutions. Aspiring to make career in software engineering with a focus on full stack development.

Phone: +91 9901437129

Earlier I worked as WordPress developer (3 Years) and I have worked as a freelancer for 15 months of time in Agix International. I am a tech realize person and have a keen interest in new technologies.

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer (FEB 2022 – OCT 2022)

The 10X Academy (Bootcamp of MERN training)

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, NodeJs, MongoDB, DSA, etc
- Fully focused on projects, assignments and programming.

Web Developer (NOV 2019 – JUL 2021)

Agix International Pvt Ltd

- I have developed 100+ websites till now
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, Bootstrap, Antd, WordPress
- I lead 4 members team with client interactions & presentations
- Check out my UI Designs in portfolio https://agixinternational.com/ourprojects/

PROJECTS

My Portfolio

Technologies are used: ReactJS

Github Link: https://github.com/SRIKRISNA/portfolio **Project Link:** https://sk-portfolio.onrender.com/

Movies App

Technologies are used: ReactJs

Github Link: https://github.com/SRIKRISNA/display_movies **Project Link:** https://srikrisna.github.io/display_movies/

 Category wise display, Search Filter, Pagination, Lazy Loading, Modal Popup Box features were added

Share Post (instaclone)

Technologies are used: ReactJs, NodeJs, ExpressJs, MongoDB **Github Link:** https://github.com/SRIKRISNA/instaclone1

Project Link: https://iinstafront.netlify.app/ **Features:** upload post, delete post, view all posts

My Store (React - Redux Toolkit)

Technologies are used: ReactJs, Redux Toolkit

Github Link: https://github.com/SRIKRISNA/reduxcart **Project Link:** https://reduxcart-p8tj.onrender.com

Functionalities: Fetch & display products from API, Add to cart, View Cart, Remove

Cart Item